[This trendy drama of romance is only for people aged 12 or older.]
[هذه الدراما الرومانسية العصرية مخصصة فقط للأشخاص الذين تبلغ أعمارهم 12 عامًا أو أكبر.]
[Once Again]
[مرة اخرى]
[Episode 2 Missing someone]
[الحلقة 2 مفقود شخص ما]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Who is it?
من هذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
This is Kang Ji-hoon.
هذا كانغ جي - هون.
[Theory and Case Law]
[النظرية والسوابق القضائية]
What?
ماذا؟
You must have called the wrong number.
يجب أن تكون قد اتصلت بالرقم الخطأ.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Bye.
وداعا.
Hey, Kang Ji-hoon.
مرحبًا ، كانغ جي - هون.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
All right. All right.
حسنا.  حسنا.
I bought a camera today. Take a photo as a souvenir.
اشتريت كاميرا اليوم.  التقط صورة كتذكار.
You bought it?
أنت إشتريتها؟
Don't touch it. It'll get tainted.
لا تلمسه.  سوف تتلوث.
You punk.
انت فاسق.
Take it respectfully with both hands.
خذها باحترام بكلتا يديك.
This is the first work I took with this camera.
هذا هو أول عمل قمت به بهذه الكاميرا.
Come out for a beer.
اخرج لتناول الجعة.
Okay.
تمام.
How is your studying going?
كيف تجري دراستك؟
It's alright. What about you?
لا بأس.  وماذا عنك؟
Me?
أنا؟
I just realized something recently.
لقد أدركت شيئًا مؤخرًا.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I bet I was an anchovy in my previous life.
أراهن أنني كنت أنشوفة في حياتي السابقة.
Otherwise, why is my brain full of shit?
خلاف ذلك ، لماذا عقلي مليء بالقرف؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
No matter how hard I try, I don't think I can pass the bar exam.
بغض النظر عن مدى صعوبة المحاولة ، لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع اجتياز اختبار المحاماة.
I don't think my name is Joo Hyeong-jin. I should be called Joo Anchovy.
لا أعتقد أن اسمي هو Joo Hyeong-jin.  يجب أن يُدعى جو أنشوفي.
It's been 27 years and I've finally realized it.
لقد مرت 27 عامًا وأدركت ذلك أخيرًا.
We're submitting the application form tomorrow. You're such a jinx.
سنرسل نموذج الطلب غدًا.  أنت مثل النحس.
You know, my instincts are always right.
كما تعلم ، غرائزي دائما على حق.
You'll make it this time.
ستفعلها هذه المرة.
You can't just abandon me after passing the exam.
لا يمكنك التخلي عني بعد اجتياز الامتحان.
Forget it. We can make it together.
انسى ذلك.  يمكننا أن نجعلها معا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
There are so many stars in the sky.
هناك الكثير من النجوم في السماء.
Hyeong-jin, life is so boring.
هيونغ جين ، الحياة مملة للغاية.
Of course it's boring to be an examinee.
بالطبع من الممل أن تكون ممتحناً.
Why don't you go on a date?
لماذا لا تذهب في موعد؟
You're being paranoid.
أنت تصاب بجنون العظمة.
How can I date in this situation?
كيف يمكنني المواعدة في هذه الحالة؟
I'm just like you.
انا مثلك تماما.
Don't be like that. Go on a date just like I do.
لا تكن هكذا.  اذهب في موعد مثلما أفعل.
Dating is one of the tests, okay?
المواعدة هي أحد الاختبارات ، حسنًا؟
We have to prepare for it.
علينا الاستعداد لذلك.
Who would like someone like me?
من يود شخص مثلي؟
Goodness.
صلاح.
Come to think of it,
تعال نفكر بها،
I almost forgot what time it was that someone confessed to me.
كدت أنسى الوقت الذي اعترف فيه أحد لي.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
You're just too pessimistic.
أنت فقط متشائم للغاية.
I don't feel like drinking.
لا أشعر بالرغبة في الشرب.
I'm leaving. See you tomorrow.
سأغادر.  أراك غدا.
Okay.
تمام.
Sleep well. Don't be late tomorrow.
نم جيداً.  لا تتأخر غدًا.
How can you eat ice cream on such a cold day?
كيف يمكنك أن تأكل الآيس كريم في مثل هذا اليوم البارد؟
Ice cream is better served in a cold weather.
يتم تقديم الآيس كريم بشكل أفضل في الطقس البارد.
I'll treat you.
سوف يعاملك.
[Store]
[متجر]
What?
ماذا؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I forgot my application form.
لقد نسيت نموذج الطلب الخاص بي.
Application form?
استمارة التقديم؟
Anyway, I can't stand my anchovy brain.
على أي حال ، لا يمكنني تحمل دماغي الأنشوجة.
Let's eat it next time.
دعونا نأكله في المرة القادمة.
You'll break ice cream's heart.
ستكسر قلب الآيس كريم.
Fetching the application form doesn't conflict with the ice cream.
إحضار نموذج الطلب لا يتعارض مع الآيس كريم.
Still the old flavor. See you later.
لا تزال النكهة القديمة.  أراك لاحقًا.
Don't leave first.
لا ترحل أولاً.
If you dare to waste time, I will leave you behind.
إذا كنت تجرؤ على إضاعة الوقت ، سأتركك ورائك.
Do you loathe it?
هل تكرهها؟
Yes.
نعم.
Is it good?
هل هذا جيد؟
Isn't it too cold?
أليس الجو باردا جدا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Shouldn't you be at school now?
ألا يجب أن تكون في المدرسة الآن؟
It's holiday.
انها عطلة.
I see.
أرى.
Are you going to the academy?
هل انت ذاهب الى الاكاديمية؟
Yes.
نعم.
Then why are you here?
ثم لماذا أنت هنا؟
The owner of this ice cream has a bad temper.
صاحب هذا الآيس كريم مزاج سيء.
Do you want it?
هل تريده؟
How old are you?
كم عمرك؟
Ten years old.
يبلغ من العمر عشر سنوات.
A baby face.
وجه طفل.
What?
ماذا؟
You don't look like ten years old. It's a compliment.
لا تبدو وكأنك تبلغ من العمر عشر سنوات.  إنه إطراء.
You have to study hard.
يجب عليك الدراسة بجد.
How could you forget the application form on the submitting day?
كيف تنسى استمارة الطلب في يوم التقديم؟
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
You've been making fun of me all day. Aren't you done?
لقد كنت تسخر مني طوال اليوم.  ألم تنته؟
You're so funny.
أنت مضحك جدا.
Anyway, think of your own temper.
على أي حال ، فكر في أعصابك.
Hello, pot. I'm kettle.
مرحبا يا وعاء.  أنا غلاية.
As long as I submitted it successfully.
طالما قمت بتقديمه بنجاح.
I was going to leave you behind.
كنت سأتركك ورائك.
I waited for you because I'm a nice person.
لقد انتظرتك لأني شخص لطيف.
I'm so touched by your temper.
أنا متأثر جدًا بمزاجك.
[Room 304]
[الغرفة 304]
I think your phone is ringing.
أعتقد أن هاتفك يرن.
My phone?
هاتفي؟
Get some rest.
خذ قسطا من الراحة.
Okay, you too.
حسنا انت ايضا.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Sir.
سيد.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Sir, is that you?
سيدي ، هل هذا أنت؟
It's you, isn't it?
إنه أنت ، أليس كذلك؟
You're him, right?
أنت هو حق؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Are you the one who called me yesterday?
هل أنت من اتصل بي البارحة؟
You have the wrong number.
لديك الرقم الخطأ.
Please check the number again.
يرجى التحقق من الرقم مرة أخرى.
I'm right.
أنا على حق.
You are Kang Ji-hoon that I've been missing.
أنت كانغ جي - هون الذي كنت في عداد المفقودين.
What?
ماذا؟
Sir, are you listening?
سيدي ، هل تسمع؟
Stop joking. I'm busy.
توقف عن المزاح.  أنا مشغول.
-Bye. -I'm sorry.
-وداعا.  -أنا آسف.
It's okay. Sometimes we do have the wrong number.
حسنا.  أحيانًا يكون لدينا الرقم الخطأ.
I'm really sorry.
أنا حقا آسف.
What?
ماذا؟
I don't understand what you're talking about.
أنا لا أفهم ما الذي تتحدث عنه.
I know it's all my fault.
أعلم أن هذا كله خطأي.
But I hope you won't blame me.
لكن آمل ألا تلومني.
I know it's selfish of me to say this,
أعلم أنه من الأناني أن أقول هذا ،
but I'm so sad.
لكن انا حزين جدا.
That's why I feel sorry for you.
لهذا أشعر بالأسف من أجلك.
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
Anyway, please calm down.
على أي حال ، من فضلك اهدأ.
Bye.
وداعا.
Wait. Please listen.
انتظر.  إستمع من فضلك.
I'm busy. Bye.
أنا مشغول.  وداعا.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Right now. Eat it now.
فى الحال.  أكله الآن.
-What are you thinking about? -What?
-بم تفكر؟  -ماذا او ما؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Hyeong-jin.
هيونغ جين.
Someone keeps apologizing to me.
شخص ما يعتذر لي باستمرار.
Apologize to you? Why?
أعتذر لك؟  لماذا ا؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
At first, I thought it was a joke.
في البداية اعتقدت أنها مزحة.
How should I put it?
كيف يجب ان اضعها؟
But he didn't sound like he was joking.
لكنه لم يبدو أنه كان يمزح.
Really? Did you lend your money?
هل حقا؟  هل أقرضت أموالك؟
No, it's not like that.
لا ، ليس الأمر كذلك.
Kang Ji-hoon, be careful.
كانغ جي هون ، كن حذرًا.
It might be a new swindle.
قد يكون خداع جديد.
You study law.
أنت تدرس القانون.
It'd be funny for you to be fooled.
سيكون من المضحك أن تنخدع.
I told you it's not like that.
أخبرتك أن الأمر ليس كذلك.
You're perfectly soft-hearted to be traped.
أنت طيب القلب تمامًا ليتم محاصرتك.
If I were a liar,
لو كنت كاذبا
I would've robbed you and run away.
كنت سأسرقك وأهرب.
What are you waiting for? The noodles are getting soggy.
ماذا تنتظر؟  المعكرونة تصبح فطيرة.
I'll eat it all if you won't.
سآكلها كلها إذا لم تفعل.
Forget it. I don't want to talk to you.
انسى ذلك.  لا اريد التحدث معك.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
I just had two bites.
لقد تناولت فقط عضتين.
If some kimchi was added in the noodles, I could at least have some kimchi.
إذا تمت إضافة بعض الكيمتشي في المعكرونة ، يمكنني على الأقل الحصول على بعض الكيمتشي.
It's none of my business.
إنه ليس من شأنى.
I only had two bites. What a bad temper.
لقد تناولت عضتين فقط.  يا له من مزاج سيء.
Is there anything else to eat?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر للأكل؟
Help!
مساعدة!
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Darn it.
رتقها.
Hey!
يا!
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Yes.
نعم.
Aren't you the boy from that day?
ألست الفتى من ذلك اليوم؟
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
No.
رقم.
That's a relief.
هذا مريح.
Come on. I'll take you home.
هيا.  سوف آخذك للمنزل.
Where do you live?
أين تعيش؟
I'm afraid of going home.
أخشى العودة إلى المنزل.
Is no one home?
ألا يوجد أحد في المنزل؟
Dad's on a business trip.
أبي في رحلة عمل.
Mom's going to work. She'll be back tomorrow morning.
أمي ذاهبة إلى العمل.  سوف تعود صباح الغد.
Really?
هل حقا؟
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
You can't sleep?
لا تستطيع النوم؟
Sir.
سيد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're awake?
انت مستيقظ؟
Did you sleep well last night?
هل نمت جيدا الليلة الماضية؟
I'll wash my face and take you home.
سأغسل وجهي وأخذك إلى المنزل.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
[Criminal Law]
[قانون جنائي]
[Thank you, sir.]
[شكرا لك سيدي.]
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
Who is he?
من هذا؟
Who is this kid?
من هذا الطفل؟
I don't think he's your son.
لا أعتقد أنه ابنك.
Is he your nephew?
هل هو ابن أخيك؟
Well, kind of.
كذلك نوع من.
You're so cute. How old are you?
انت لطيف جدا.  كم عمرك؟
Ten years old.
يبلغ من العمر عشر سنوات.
I'm going out.
أنا ذاهب للخارج.
Bye.
وداعا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Goodness.
صلاح.
I used to be this cute.
اعتدت أن أكون هذا لطيف.
Go in and study.
اذهب وادرس.
I can go back by myself from here.
يمكنني العودة بنفسي من هنا.
Can you?
هل تستطيع؟
Okay, bye.
حسنًا ، إلى اللقاء.
Okay.
تمام.
He looks unfamiliar. Is he new here?
يبدو غير مألوف.  هل هو جديد هنا؟
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
Why are you blushing?
لماذا تحمر خجلا؟
You got the wrong person.
لقد حصلت على الشخص الخطأ.
[2007 Calendar]
[تقويم 2007]
2007?
2007؟
What are you doing in my room?
ماذا تفعل في غرفتي؟
Have you seen me before?
هل رأيتني من قبل؟
I'll just stay here a little longer before I leave.
سأبقى هنا لفترة أطول قليلاً قبل أن أغادر.
Why are you always staring at me?
لماذا تحدق بي دائما؟